A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Harry F. Byrd, 1926-1930
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Subject files, 1926-1930., Extent: 39.75 cu. ft. (106 boxes). (Box Boxes 1-105, 141)
  - S, 1926 August - September. (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - S, 1926 October - December. (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - S, 1926 December - 1927 January. (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - S, 1927 February - April. (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - S, 1927 May - June. (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - S, 1927 July - December. (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - S, 1928 January - August. (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - S, 1928 September - 1929 May. (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - S, 1929 June - 1930 January. (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Schools, 1928. (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Scott County disaster, 1929. (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Scouts, Boy, 1926 - 1929. (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Scribners, 1927 - 1928. (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Seafood Commission, 1927 - 1928. (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1927 - 1929. (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of State (US), 1925 - 1928 July. (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of State (US), 1928 August - 1930 January. (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Sesquicentennial, 1925. (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Sesquicentennial, 1926 January - July. (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Sesquicentennial, 1926 August - September. (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Sesquicentennial, 1927 May. (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Sesquicentennial, Battle of Saratoga (FL), 1927. (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Shenandoah Assembly, 1928. (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Shepperd, Gwynn T., 1928. (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Social Work National Conference, 1926 - 1929. (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Soldiers Home (R.E. Lee Camp), 1925-1930. (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Soldiers Home, National (Hampton, Va.), 1927-1929. (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Sons of American Revolution, 1928. (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Sons of Confederate Veterans, 1927-1928. (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Southern Appalachian Power Conference, 1927-1928. (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Southern Commerical Congress, 1926-1928. (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Southern Exposition, 1926. (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Southern Forestry Congress, 1927. (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Southern Forestry Congress, 1928. (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Southern Forestry Congress, 1929. (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Standardization Board (Advisory), 1926. (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - State Board of Canvassers, 1926-1928. (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - State Board of Education, 1926. (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - State Board of Education, 1926. (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - State Board of Education, 1927. (Box 84, Folder 2-3)
  - State Board of Education, 1928. (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - State Board of Pharmacy, 1926-1927. (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - State Board of Pharmacy, 1927-1928. (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - State Board of Public Welfare, 1926. (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - State Board of Public Welfare, 1927 January - August. (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - State Board of Public Welfare, 1927 September - December. (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - State Board of Public Welfare, 1928-1930. (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - State Board of Public Welfare, Publications, 1925-1928. (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - State Board of Public Welfare, WW Veterans Service Division, 1928-1930. (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - State Bureau of Criminal Investigation, 1927. (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - State Park Association, 1929. (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - State Comptroller, Account Procedures, 1928. (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - State Comptroller, 1927-1929. (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1926-1927. (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1928 January - February. (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1928 March - December. (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1929 January - April. (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1929 May - June. (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1929 July - September. (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1929 October - December. (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - State Corporation Commission, Advisory and Research Commission, etc., 1928. (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - State Corporation Commission, Advisory and Research Commission, etc., 1929. (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - State Corporation Commission, Banking Commission, Annual reports, 1926-1927. (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - State Corporation Commission, Banking Commission, 1926-1929. (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - State Corporation Commission, Bureau of Insurance, 1927-1929. (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - State Corporation Commission, Lake Cargo Coal Case, 1926-1928. (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - State Corporation Commission, Recommendations for appointments, 1927-1928. (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - State Corporation Commission, Rural electrification, 1929. (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - State Corporation Commission, Transfer, 1926. (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - State Corporation Commission, Transfer, 1926 August - 1927 March. (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - State Corporation Commission, Transfer, 1927 April - December. (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - State Corporation Commission, Water Power Development Commission, 1926. (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - State Corporation Commission, Water power legislation, 1926-1929. (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - State Depositories, 1927 - 1928 June. (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - State Depositories, 1928 July - 1930 January. (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - State Entomologists, 1926-1928. (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - State Fair Association, 1926-1929. (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - State Farm for Defective Misdemeanants, 1926-1929. (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - State Financial Procedure, 1928-1929. (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - State Geologist, 1926-1929. (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - State Government Statistics (other states), 1926-1927. (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - State Horticultural Society, 1926-1929. (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - State Horticultural Society, Annual meetings, 1927-1928. (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - State Horticultural Society, 1928-1929. (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - State Library, 1927. (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - State Library, 1928. (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - State Library, 1929-1930. (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - State Library, Publications, 1927-1928. (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - State Library Board, 1926-1929. (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - State Museum, 1925-1926. (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - State Office Building, 1925-1929. (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - State Port Authority, 1926. (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - State Port Authority, 1927. (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - State Port Authority, Report, 1927. (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - State Port Authority, 1928 January - June. (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - State Port Authority, 1928 July - December. (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - State Port Authority, 1929-1930. (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - State Port Authority, Publication, The Ports of Norfolk, Portsmouth and Newport News, 1927. (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - State Port Authority, Transfer, 1926-1927. (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - State seal, 1928-1929. (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - State survey, 1927-1929. (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - State survey, NY Bureau of Municipal Research, 1926. (Box 90, Folder 6-7)
  - State survey, NY Bureau of Municipal Research, 1927. (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - State Teachers College, East Radford, 1926-1929. (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - State Teachers College, Farmville, 1926-1929. (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - State Teachers College, Fredericksburg, 1926-1928. (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - State Teachers College, Harrisonburg, 1926-1929. (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - State Teachers College, Miscellaneous, 1926-1929. (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - State Tour, 1926. (Box 91, Folder 7-8)
  - State Veterinarian, 1926-1929. (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Statistics and tables, 1926-1927. (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Stone Mountain Memorial (Ga.), 1924-1925. (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Stone Mountain Memorial (Ga.), 1926-1929. (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Stream pollution, 1926-1929. (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Street and Highway Safety National Conference, 1926. (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Student Internaitonal Union, 1928. (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Summer White House, 1928-1929. (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Swannanoa Country Club, 1928. (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - T, 1926 January - May. (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - T, 1926 June - December. (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - T, 1927 January - April. (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - T, 1927 May - December. (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - T, 1928. (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - T, 1929. (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Tax Board, 1926. (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Tax Commission, 1926 January - April. (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Tax Commission, 1926 May - July. (Box 92, Folder 14-15)
  - Tax Commission, 1926 August - September. (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Tax Commission, 1926 October - December. (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Tax Commission, 1927 January - February. (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Tax Commission, 1927 March - June. (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Tax Commission, 1927 July - November. (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Tax Commission, 1927 December. (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Tax Commission, 1928 January - February. (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Tax Commission, 1928 March - July. (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Tax Commission, 1928 July - December. (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Tax Commission, 1929 Januiary - March. (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Tax Commission, 1929 April - June. (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Tax Commission, 1929 July - 1930 January. (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Tax Law Codification Commission, 1926-1927. (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Taxes, 1925 November - December. (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Taxes, 1925 December. (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Taxes, 1926 January. (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Taxes, 1926 February - March. (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Taxes, 1926 April - December. (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Taxes, 1927 January. (Box 95, Folder 3-4)
  - Taxes, 1927 February. (Box 95, Folder 5-6)
  - Taxes, 1927 March - April. (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Taxes, 1927 May - September. (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Taxes, 1927 October - December. (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Taxes, Cards to Treasurers, 1927 October - November. (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Taxes, 1928. (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Taxes, 1929 January - April. (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Taxes, 1929 May - December. (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Taxes, Letter from other Governors, 1929. (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Taxes, Bank taxes 1927-1928. (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Taxes, Hotel taxes, 1926-1928. (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Taxes, Railroad taxes, 1927-1928. (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Taxes, Virginia Tax Laws, 1926. (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Taylor, George E., 1927. (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Telephone, 1926. (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Texas, Governor, 1928. (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Trips, 1926. (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Tuition fees, 1927-1928. (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - U, 1926-1929. (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - University of Virginia, 1921, 1926. (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - University of Virginia, 1927 January - April. (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - University of Virginia, 1927 May - August. (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - University of Virginia, 1927 September - December. (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - University of Virginia, 1928. (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - University of Virginia, 1928-1929. (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - University of Virginia Record, Extension Series, 1921-1928. (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - University of Virginia, Controversy with Dr. Hepburn, 1928-1929. (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - University Hospital, 1930. (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Conference on Education, Rehabilitation, Reclamation, and Recreation, 1925-1926. (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Good Roads Association, 1926. (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Good Roads Association, 1927. (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Good Roads Association, 1928. (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Good Roads Association, 1929. (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Levies, Approrpiations, 1926. (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Utah, Governor, 1929. (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - V, 1926-1929. (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Valley Forge (Pa.), 1927-1929. (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Vermont, Governor, 1929. (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Vermont party, 1929. (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Veterans Bureau, 1927-1930. (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Academy of Science, 1926-1929. (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Cirginia Bureau of Industrial Rehabilitation, 1926. (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Bureau of Research, 1929. (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Commission for the Blind, 1926-1927. (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Commission for the Blind, 1928-1929. (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Committee on Distributions, 1926. (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Council on Religious Education, 1928-1929. (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Historical Society, 1928-1930. (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Home and Industrial School for Girls, 1926-1929. (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Industrial School for Boys, 1926-1927. (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Industrial School for Colored Girls and Manual Labor School for Colored Boys, 1923, 1927-1929. (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Association, 1929. (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1925-1926. (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1927. (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1928. (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1929-1930. (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Municipal Review, 1928-1929. (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Museum of Natural History, 1926-1928. (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute, 1926-1930. (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1926-1927. (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1928. (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1929-1930. (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Extension Division, 1926-1927. (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Annual report of the Director of Extension Work in Virginia, 1924 December - 1925 November. (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Annual report of the Director of Extension Work in Virginia, 1925 December - 1926 November. (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Annual report of the Director of Extension Work in Virginia, 1926 December - 1927 November. (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Annual report of the Director of Extension Work in Virginia, 1927 December - 1928 November. (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Bulletins, 1928-1929. (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Real Estate Commission, 1926-1929. (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Virginia, Reports, 1927. (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Virginia School for Colored Deaf and Blind Children, 1926-1929. (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Virginia School for Deaf and Blind Children, 1926-1929. (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Social Science Association, 1929. (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Virginia State Diseased and Crippled Children's Hospital, 1926-1929. (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Truck Experiment Station, 1926-1929. (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Vital Statistics, Bureau of, 1926. (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - W, 1925-1926 March. (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - W, 1926 April - June. (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - W, 1926 July - September. (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - W, 1926 October - December. (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - W, 1927 January - February. (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - W, 1927 March. (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - W, 1927 April - June. (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - W, 1927 July - September. (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - W, 1927 October - December. (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - W, 1928. (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - W, 1929. (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - War Department, 1927-1929. (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - War Memorial Commission, 1926 - 1928 January. (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - War Memorial Commission, 1928 January. (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - War Memorial Commission, 1928 January - April. (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Washington, George, Celebration in Alexandria (Va.), 1928-1929. (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Washington, George, Miscellaneous, 1928-1929. (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Washington Industrial Accident Prevention Conference, 1926. (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Washington and Lee (University), 1929. (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Weights and Measures, 1926. (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - West Point Cadets, 1927-1930. (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - West Virginia, Governor, 1927-1929. (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - William and Mary, College of, 1925-1927. (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - William and Mary, College of, 1928-1929. (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Williamsburg (Colonial Williamsburg) restoration, 1927-1929. (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, Memorial, 1927-1929. (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Wisconsin, Governor, 1929. (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - World Conference on Adult Education, 1929. (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - World Peace, 1926-1929. (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - World War I trophies, 1926-1929. (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Wyoming, Governor, 1929. (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Wytheville (Va.) lynching, 1927-1928. (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - X, Y, Z, 1926-1929. (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Yorktown (Va.) Arsenal, 1927 January - May. (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Yorktown (Va.) Arsenal, 1927 June - 1928 April. (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Yorktown (Va.) Forum, 1926-1928. (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Oversize, Agriculture - C (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Oversize, Chamber of Commerce - Conservation and Development, Commission (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Oversize, Congress of Agriculture - Highway Commission (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Oversize, Highway Commission - Misc. correspondence (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Oversize, Motor Vehicle Commission - Soldiers Home, National (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Oversize, State Comptroller (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Oversize, State Corporation Commission - State Port Authority (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Oversize, Tax Charts - Virginia Industrial School for Boys (Box 141, Folder 8)
- Series II: Pardons, Requisitions, and Prison Affairs, 1922-1926., Extent: cu. ft. ( boxes) (Box Boxes 106-)
  The Pardons and Requisitions series, 1922-1926, is housed in twenty-three archival boxes and is arranged into three subseries. Subseries have been designated for: A. Pardons; B. Requisitions; and C. Prison Affairs.
  Included are arrest warrants, correspondence, court orders, extradition requisitions, pardon applications, petitions, prison records, telegrams, and newspaper clippings. Subseries A: Pardons is arranged alphabetically by last name and includes letters from family members asking for pardons of relatives; letters from prisoners asking for pardons; letters from politicians on behalf of prisoners; and petitions asking for pardons of prisoners. The records include the name of prisoner, date committed, age, occupation, court, crime, and term information.
  Subseries B: Requisitions, is arranged alphabetically by last name and includes correspondence, telegrams, and extradition requisitions to and from Virginia.
  Subseries C: Prison Affairs.
  Arranged into three subseries: Subseries A: Pardons, Subseries B: Requisitions, and Subseries C: Prison Affairs.
  - Subseries A. Pardons
    - Adams (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Adkins (Atkins), Charles (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Adkins - Alford (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Allen (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Alley - Andrews (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Apperson - Ayers (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Badham - Banaster (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Barberry - Baylor (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Beaty - Bevins (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Bibb - Bishop (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Blaine - Blythe (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Bodenhamer - Boyles (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Brady - Brewer (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Brickhouse - Britt (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Broaddus - Broughman (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Brown, Alfred - Brown, Jimmie (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Brown, R.P. - Brown, William (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Brush - Bucklin (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Bullifant - Byrd (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Campbell - Cantwell (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Caraway - Carroll (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Carter (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Cash - Cave (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Chambliss - Chaplin (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Chellis - Christian (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Claiborne - Clements (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Click - Clouser (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Cobbs - Coles (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Colley - Colvin (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Combs - Cooper (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Coram - Cox (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Craddock - Crawford (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Creasy - Crumby (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Currier, Mae (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Dalton - Davenport (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Davis, Eddie - Davis, Oliver (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Pendleton - Day (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Dean - DeRosa (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Dickerson - Dix (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Dobbins - Doyle (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Driver - Dye (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Eades - Edwards (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Elliott - Ellis (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Emory - Enroughty (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Eppes - Ezzle (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Fairfax - Ferribee (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Finch - Flynn (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Foley - Fox (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Fralin - Frazier (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - French - Funkhouser (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Gaines - Garrett, Larkin (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Garrett, Robert O. (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Garrison - Gay (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Gee - Gilliam (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Glass - Governor (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Grabill - Graybeal (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Green - Gregory (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Griffin - Gydosh (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Haggard - Hall, Kelly (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Hall, Leslie - Hall, Wesley (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Ham - Harmon (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Harper - Harris, Gid (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Harris, Henry - Harrison (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Harrold - Hazzard (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Heavener - Hendricks (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Henry - Hesselschwert (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Hickman - Hill (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Hilliards - Hogan (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Hoke - Houff (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Housden - Hudson (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Hughes - Hurt (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Irby - Irvin (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Jackson (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Jamerson - Jewell (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, Bernard - Johnson, Harvey (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Jessee - Johnson, Wyman (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Jones, Andrew - Jones, Jesse (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Jones, Jim - Jones, W. H. (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Joo - Joyner (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Keaton - Kellum (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Kelly - Keys (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Kidwell - Kinsey (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Kirby - Krogstad (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Lam - Lantz (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Larimer - Layne (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Lecours - Lee (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Lefler - Lewis (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Lilly - Liverman (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Lockey - Looney (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Louis - Lumsford (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - McCauley - McDorman (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - McFall - McSherry (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Mabie - Manton (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Marsh - Martin, Charles (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Martin, Earle - Martin, Thomas (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Mason - Maupin (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Mawyer - Mays (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Meadows - Medlin (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Melson - Meyers (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Mika - Miller (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Millner - Miltz (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Mimms - Minton (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Mitchell (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Monroe - Moore (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Morgan (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Morris (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Morrisette - Moxley (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Mullens - Mullins (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Mumaw - Myers (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Nagle - Nash (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Neal - Nelson (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Newcomb - Newton (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Nicholas - Nowlin (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - O (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Pace - Palmer (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Pannell - Patton (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Payne (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Peace - Petzold (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Phelps - Pierce (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Pifer - Pitchford (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Plaster - Pomerie (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Pool - Powell (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Pretlow - Putnam (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Q (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Racey - Raynes (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Reade - Reynolds (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Rhinehart - Riley (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Roadcap - Robinson (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Rochedieu - Roman (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Ronk - Rowlett (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Rudd - Ryce (Box 119, Folder 9)